Miscellaneous Art Exhibition Catalog Collection
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: M-O, Series 5:
  - New Gallery, 600 Madison Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Jan Matulka and James Chapin, from Feb. 2, 1924 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - New School for Social Research, 66 W. 12th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Exhibition of Drawings and Etchings by Kurt Seligmann, March 18-31, 1949 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - New York League for the Hard of Hearing, 126 E. 59th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Paintings by Alice Beach Winter, April 17-30 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - New York Society of Painters (Box 3)
    - Second Annual Exhibition, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - New York Water Color Club (Box 3)
    - Eighteenth Annual Exhibition, November 2-24, 1907 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Newark Museum (Box 4)
    - American Primitives, November 4, 1930-February 1, 1931 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - American Folk Sculpture, October 20, 1931-January 31, 1932 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Nippon Club, 161 W. 93rd St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Special Exhibition of Works by Noboru Foujioka, April 19-27 [annotated 30], 1924 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Number 10 Gallery, 19 East 56th Street, New York City (Box 4)
    - Water Colors, Drawings, Oils, November 1-15, [1941] (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Ortgies & Co.'s, 845 and 847 Broadway (Box 4)
    - Catalogue of Finished Pictures, Studies and Sketches, Works of Sanford R. Gifford, N.A., Deceased, March 6, 1884 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: P-R, Series 6:
  - Palace of Fine Arts, San Francisco, CA. (Box 4)
    - Official Art Catalogue: Golden Gate International Exposition, 1940 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Palette Club (Box 4)
    - Tenth Annual Exhibition, December 1, 1892 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries Inc., 30 East 57th Street, New York (Box 4)
    - Eminent Modern Paintings and Works by XIX Century Artists, March 16, 1944 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Peck's Art Rooms, 368 Main St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by Mr. and Mrs. J. B. Morse, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - The Pettes Collection of High Class Water Colors, January 15-25, 1896 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Penguin Club, 8 E. 15th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - [Invitation to participate] Temporary Exhibition at the Gallery of the Penguin, Special Meeting to discuss particulars, March 13 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of the Vorticists at the Penguin, beginning January 10, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Contemporary Art, beginning March 16, 1918 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings, Drawings, Etchings, etc. by Horace Brodzky, beginning April 8, 1918 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Paintings, Sculpture, Etc. by A Temporary Group, beginning April 5, 1919 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Box 4)
    - Charter, By-Laws, and Standing Regulations, 1813 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Tenth Annual Exhibition, May 1821 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Robert Street's Exhibition, November 18, 1840 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Paintings, Statues, and Casts, 1843 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Act of Incorporation and Standing Regulation, 1847 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Thirty-Third Annual Exhibition, 1856 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Act of Incorporation and By-Laws and Ordinances, 1877 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Act of Incorporation and By-Laws and Ordinances, 1885 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings and Drawings Showing the Later Tendencies in Art, April 16-May 15, 1921 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Contemporary European Paintings and Sculpture, April 11-May 9, 1923 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Catalogue of the One-Hundred-and-Twenty-Second Annual Exhibition of the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, January 30-March 20, 1927 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - People's Art Guild, 918 Caudwell Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Exhibition of Paintings, Etchings, and Drawings by John Sloan, held at the Hudson Guild under the auspices of the People's Art Guild, February 10-April 10 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Modern Art Exhibition at the Parish House of the Church of the Ascension, during January and February 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Petrus Stuyvesant Club, 129 E. 10th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Paintings by Hamilton Easter Field and of Carvings by Robert Laurent, February 14-26, 1916 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Pierre Matisse (Box 4)
    - Artists in Exile, March 3-28, 1942 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Powell Gallery, 983 6th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - The 5th Annual Exhibition and Sale of Thumb Box Sketches, November 6-December 30 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Small Pictures by Prominent Painters, October 29-November 15, 1919 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Pratt Institute Art Gallery, Brooklyn, N.Y. (Box 4)
    - Nineteen Paintings by William Ritschel, February 8-28, 1916 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings [by] Irving R. Heitkamp, May 8-26, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Original Drawings and Studies for Mural Decorations by Violet Oakley, October 13 [annotated 15]-31, 1919 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings Illustrating Protective Coloration in Nature by Abbott H. Thayer and Gerald H. Thayer, January 5-28, 1920 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Illustrations by N. C. Wyeth, February 13-March 6 [annotated 13], 1920 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Painters and Sculptors Third Exhibition, February 5-23, 1924 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Ralston Galleries, 567 5th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Paintings by Jonas Lie, March 29-April 10, 1915 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - List of the Complete Works of Elizabeth Gulland, April 1916 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by the Late F. Hopkinson Smith, January 7-19, 1918 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Resettlement Administration, Washington D.C. (Box 4)
    - America's Land, 1936 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Robert C. Vose Galleries, 320 Boylston St., 398 Boylston St. and 559 Boylston St., Boston (Box 4)
    - Paintings Comprising the Latest Work of F.K.M. Rehn and Charles R. Peirce, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Watercolors by J. A. S. Monks, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - The Latest Works of Mary L. Macomber, March 3-15, 1913 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Albert Herter and Adele Herter, November 20-December 8, [1934] (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - [Invitation] The Art of Mickey Mouse and other Drawings by Walt Disney, March 18-April 13, [1935] (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - William Meyerowitz, July 1941 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Rockport Art Association, Rockport, Massachusetts (Box 4)
    - Artists of the Rockport Art Association, 1946 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Rowlands Galleries, 431 Boylston St., Boston (Box 4)
    - Pictures by Edmund C. Tarbell, February 20-March 2, 1907 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: S-T, Series 7:
  - Salmagundi Club, 47 5th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Salmagundi Club, undated (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Pictures by Jas. E. Fraser and Paintings by Ernest Albert, Elliott Clark, John Folinsbee, Leon Kroll, Louis Kronberg, Robert Vonnoh, March 22-April 3 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Ernest, Albert Alexander Bower, Howard Giles, Oliver Dennett Frover, Victor Higgins, Walter Ufer and Robert Vonnoh, March 21-April 2 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Salmagundian, May 1950 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Samuel Schwartz's Sons & Co., 290 5th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Paintings by Frank W. Rogers, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Schultheis' Galleries, 142 Fulton St., Brooklyn, N.Y. (Box 4)
    - Paintings by Robert Fletcher Gilder, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Scott & Fowles, 590 5th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Small Collection of Contemporary Art in America, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - [Announcement] First Exhibition of Original Works by Maxfield Parrish, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Water Color Drawings by Kay Nielsen with an introduction by Martin Birnbaum, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Catalogue of an Exhibition of Sculpture and Drawings by Elie Nadelman, 1917 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Sculptors' Gallery, 152 E. 40th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Sculpture, Paintings and Drawings by Members of the Art Schools of New York, May 7-20, 1923 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Sculptors Guild, 52 West Eighth Street, New York City (Box 4)
    - Outdoor Sculpture Exhibition, April 12-May 1938 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Societe Anonyme (Museum of Modern Art), 19 E. 47th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Matisse, Gris, Derain, Picasso, Braque, Rivera, Gleizes, Villon at its 6th Exhibition, December 15, 1920-February 1, 1921 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Societe Du Salon D'Automne, Paris (Box 4)
    - Catalogue of Painting, Sculpture, Architecture, and Decorative Art, October 18-November 25, 1905 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Painting, Sculpture, Architecture, and Decorative Art, October 1-November 8, 1909 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Society of Independent Artists, 20 West 31st Street, New York City (Box 4)
    - [Brochure] Exhibition of 1917, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Catalogue of the First Annual Exhibition, April 10-May 6, 1917 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Third Annual Exhibition, March 28-April 14, 1919 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Fourth Annual Exhibition, March 11-April 1, 1920 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Fifth Annual Exhibition, February 26-March 24, 1921 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Sixth Annual Exhibition, March 11-April 2, 1922 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Seventh Annual Exhibition, February 24-March 18, 1923 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Eighth Annual Exhibition, March 7-March 30, 1924 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Ninth Annual Exhibition, March 6-March 29, 1925 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Tenth Annual Exhibition, March 5-March 28, 1926 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 11th Annual Exhibition, March 11-April 3, 1927 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 12th Annual Exhibition, March 9-April 1, 1928 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 13th Annual Exhibition, March 8-March 31, 1929 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 14th Annual Exhibition, March 1-30, 1930 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 15th Annual Exhibition, March 7-30, 1931 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - A Preview of the Art of Tomorrow (23rd Annual Exhibition), March 29-April 19, 1939 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
    - Silver Jubilee Exhibition, 1942 (Box 5, Reel unfilmed)
  - St. Botolph Club, Boston, Mass. (Box 4)
    - Loan Collection of Oil Paintings by William Morris Hunt, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Oil Paintings, December 24, 1891-January 11, 1892 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by Edward D. Boit, January 30-February 11, 1893 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors and Pastels by Dodge Macknight, January 1-20, 1894 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - [Work of Joseph Lindon Smith], [November and December, 1894] (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Ten American Painters, April 21-May 12, 1902 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by the "Ten American Painters", April 26-May 13, 1905 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Joseph Lindon Smith - Egypt and Italy, January 1-20, 1906 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Work of Howard Pyle, February 24-March 11, 1906 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - St. Mark's in the Bouwerie, 133 E. 10th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Portraits and Interpretative Paintings by Stewart Reinhart and Mark Tobey, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Lewis Edward Herzog, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Student Association of Drawing and Painting, 72 Washington Sq., New York City (Box 4)
    - First Annual Exhibition, March 19-24 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Studio Building, 51 West Tenth Street, New York City (Box 4)
    - Fifth Exhibition in New York of Pictures, the Contributions of Artists of the French, English, and Flemish Schools, 1866-1867 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Studio Gallery, 540 North Michigan Ave., Chicago (Box 4)
    - Exhibition by Chicago Artists: Art of Today-Chicago, 1933, January 21-February 18, 1933 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Thumb Box Gallery, 24 E. 49th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Wood Gaylor, February 7-19 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Boardman Robinson, January 24-February 5 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Touchstone Galleries, 11 W. 47th St., New York City (Box 4)
    - Recent Paintings in Spain by William Sanger, November 3-15 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Oil Paintings by Julie Stohr, November 17-31 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Recent paintings and Pastels by Bernard Gussow, December 13-25 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: U-Z, Series 8:
  - Union League Club, New York City (Box 4)
    - Sources of Paintings, Sculpture and Other Objects of Art in the Union League Club, undated (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Oil Paintings, January 8, 1885 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Uptown Gallery, 249 West End Avenue, New York City (Box 4)
    - Works of the Late Alfred Maurer, October 30-December 3, 1934 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Boardman Robinson, January 24-February 5 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Vassar College (Box 4)
    - A Catalogue of the Art Collection, June 28, 1864 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Wanamaker Gallery of Modern Decorative Art - Belmaison, Broadway at 9th, New York City (Box 4)
    - Second Annual Decorative Exhibition, March 1-21 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Black and White Drawings by American Artists, May 4-31 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Paintings by Eliseo Meifren [Au Quatrieme], November 17-December 17, 1916 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Second Art Students Exhibition, March 18-30, 1918 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Annual American Exhibition, January 22-February 17, 1923 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Wanamaker Regional Art Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting (Wanamaker Gallery), October 13-November 3, 1924 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - War Assets Administration, P.O. Box 216, Wall St. Station, New York City (Box 4)
    - Catalog of 117 Oil and Water Color Originals by Leading American Artists, 1948 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Weyhe Gallery, 794 Lexington Avenue, New York City (Box 4)
    - Catalogue of Fine Prints Recently Acquired, undated (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - A Choice Collection of Books and Prints, undated (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - An Exhibition of Work by Artist Members of the Stowaways, January 20-February 7, 1920 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Art Books, Prints and Drawings, Autumn 1921 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - A Short List of Books, Prints, and Drawings, Autumn 1921 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Selections From the Stock of the Weyhe Gallery, December 1934 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Fine Prints, Drawings, Water-Colors, Stencils, Painting, and Sculpture, December 1936 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Fine Prints, Drawings, Water-Colors, Stencils, Painting, and Sculpture, December 1937 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 10 West Eighth Street, New York (Box 4)
    - Exhibition of the Works of Artist Fellows of the John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, April 3-27, 1933 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Treasury Department Art Projects: Sculpture and Paintings for Federal Buildings, October 6-November 6, 1936 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - First Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Sculpture, Watercolors, and Prints, December 5, 1933-January 11, 1934 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - New York Realists: Robert Henri, George Luks, John Sloan, William Glackens, Ernest Lawson, George Bellows, Everett Shinn, Glenn O. Coleman, and Guy Pene Du Bois, February 9-March 5, 1937 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Members of the New York Chapter of Artists Equity, May 28-June 10, 1951 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Whitney-Richards Gallery, Holland House, N.Y. (Box 4)
    - [Irving Hritkamp Paintings], undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Drawings by George Bellows, December 15-31, 1915 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Whitney Studio Club also Mrs. H. P. Whitney's Studio, 147 W. 4th St. and 8 W. 8th, New York City (Box 4)
    - Paintings by John Dos Passos and Adelaide J. Lawson and Sculpture by Ruben [sic] Nakian, January 5-24 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Drawings of Boardman Robinson Including His Series of the Washington Arms Conference, March 6-26 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Marcel Duchamp, Pablo Picasso, Georges Braque Caricatures by Marius de Zayas Selected and Arranged by Charles Sheeler, February 27-March 11 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture and Drawings by Grace Mott Johnson and Drawings by Lila Wheelock, November 18-December 2 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - [Announcement] Early American Art Selected and Arranged by H. E. Schnakenberg, February 9-24 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - [Announcement] Annual Exhibition of Paintings & Sculpture by the Members of the Club, April 6-30 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Annual Exhibition Painting & Sculpture by Members of the Club, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Water Colors - Thomas H. Donnelly, Richard Lahey, Richard Marwede, Mary F. Wesselhoeft & Designs for Stained Glass by Miss Wesselhoeft (10 W. 8th St.), November 28-December 14 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings & Drawings Selected and Arranged by Mr. W. E. Hill, January 23-February 6 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Drawings and Water Colors by Arthur Faber, Thomas Hunt, George A. Picken, February 21-March 14 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by the Members of the Whitney Studio Club, April 2-30 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Overseas Exhibition of American Paintings (Mrs. H.P. Whitney's Studio), November 2-15 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Etchings and Drawings by John Sloan at Mrs. H.P. Whitney's Studio, January 26-February 6, 1916 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Introspective Art at Mrs. H. P. Whitney's Studio, March 20-April 3, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings at the Whitney Studio by Ernest Lawson and Guy Pene du Bois, three weeks beginning November 15, 1918 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Sculpture by Members of The Whitney Studio Club, December 1918 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture by Malvina Hoffman and Decorations by Arthur Crisp (Mrs. H.P. Whitney's Studio), February 25-March 18, 1919 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Drawings and Etchings [Edward Hopper and Kenneth Hayes Miller], January 14-28, 1920 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Drawings and Etchings by Olaf Olesen, John Sloan and Randall Davey, January 26-February 13, 1921 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Joseph Stella and H. E. Schnakenberg, November 7-28, 1921 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - 10th Annual Exhibition of the Whitney Studio Club, May 18-30, 1925 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - 11th Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Members of the [Whitney Studio] Club, March 8-20, 1926 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - 12th Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Members of the [Whitney Studio] Club, February 16-March 5, 1927 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Spring Exhibition - Whitney Studio Galleries [Flower Painting], 1930 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Wildenstein & Co., 647 Fifth Avenue, New York City (Box 4)
    - Third Annual Exhibition of New Society of Artists, November 15-December 15, 1921 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Tri-National Art: French, British, American, 1926 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Willard Gallery, 32East 57, New York City (Box 4)
    - David Smith, April 1950 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Williams & Everett, 190 Boylston St., Boston, Mass. (Box 4)
    - Paintings by George Fuller, May 9, 1884 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings in Oil and Pastel by Theodore Robinson and Theodore Wendel, April 1-14, 1892 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Works by Elihu Vedder, January 19-February 2, 1900 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Yale, New Haven (Box 4)
    - [Extract from the New Haven Palladium of November 30th]The Jeremiah of Washington Allston, undated (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by Colonel Trumbull, 1831 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings in the South Room of Trumbull Gallery, 1835 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by Colonel Trumbull, 1835 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings Belonging to Yale College, April 1859 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Works of Art Exhibited in the Alumni Building of Yale College, 1858 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings in the South Room of the Gallery of Yale College, April 1859 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Paintings by Colonel Trumbull, 1864 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - First Annual Exhibition of the Yale School of Fine Arts, 1867 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Manual of the Jarves Collection of Early Italian Pictures, 1868 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of Works of Art in the Permanent and Loaned Collections, 1871 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of the School of Fine Arts, June 19, 1916 (Box 4, Reel unfilmed)
  - Yamanaka Galleries, 254 5th Ave., New York City (Box 4)
    - Annual Exhibition of the Japanese Art Association - Paintings, Drawings and Photographs, etc. by the Young Japanese Artists in New York, March 12-24, 1917 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
  - Unknown Gallery Affiliation (Box 4)
    - Exhibition of reproductions of paintings by Old Masters and Modern American Painters and Illustrators, undated (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by Stanley J. Rowland, December 11-30 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Carl Sprinchorn Exhibition, 1922 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Paintings, Etchings and Drawings by Elias M. Grossman, Isaac Kostini, and Harry Daniels, January 19-February 3, 1924 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Appreciations of the Paintings of Blanche Collet Wagner, circa 1927 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Art of David Burliuk, 1930 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Zelda Fitzgerald Photographs by Marion Hines, March 29-April 30, 1934 (Box 4, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings for Paris, May 1938 (Box 4, Reel 4859)